<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Living Light Ministries Inc</title>
    <link>localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Living Light Ministries Inc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Benjamin A. Neri Ph.D</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/leadership/ben-neri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/leadership/ben-neri/</guid>
      <description>Rev. Benjamin A. Neri is married for 33 years now and a father of one, and has been in the ministry since 1971, the host of God’s Miracle Hour Radio and TV.
Broadcast aired over RPN TV – Channel 9 and Radio GMA DYSS. Saved at age 16, Pastor Ben (as bretheren call him) answered the call to the ministry and went through four years of bible training to equip himself for the task he is called to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ptra. Zenaida Y. Neri Ph.D</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/leadership/zeny-neri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/leadership/zeny-neri/</guid>
      <description>Ptra. Zenaida Y. Neri or Ate Zeny as the brethren call her, is the partner of Ptr. Ben not only as a wife and mother of their daughter Jessah Mae, but also in the work of the Lord.
Being with her husband through pioneering two churches in other parts of the Philippines, she has faithfully labored in the vision God has laid on his shoulder in taking the Gospel to people’s homes through Radio and TV since 1985 in Dumaguete City during the times of “God’s Miracle Hour” Ministry’s days of small beginnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do want to know more about Jesus?
Please feel free to contact us, we will get back to you as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daystar Children’s Mission</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/daystar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/daystar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/donate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/events/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God&#39;s Miracle Hour</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/gmh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/gmh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/history/</guid>
      <description>On August of 1987 Ptr. Ben Neri left the United States in response to the Lord’s call to go back to the Philippines to take the Airwaves for Jesus from the City of Cebu. The cradle of Roman Catholicism, since 1521, Civilization, Education and the hub of transportation and communication 2nd to Manila.
By faith, He signed contracts with radio and TV stations only looking to God as His source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media/Gallery Section</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/media/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/ministries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/ministries/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>By visiting this website, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. We may be updating this policy from time to time. We encourage users to frequently check back on this page. This was last updated on: Sunday, February 5th, 2017. 
Any data that the Living Light Ministries Inc. Official Website (https://livinglightministriesph.org) collected from its visitors shall be used primarily to give the organization&amp;rsquo;s media team and site administrators an idea of how the people use the Site, and how the site performs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statement of Faith</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/faq/</guid>
      <description>1. The Bible is Inspired The Scriptures of the entire Bible are verbally inspired of God. It was not just the ideas that were inspired; even the choice of words was inspired as the original writers were moved by God to write what He wanted them to say. We, therefore, believe that
 the Scriptures are God&amp;rsquo;s revelation of Himself to mankind, they are infallible (never wrong), and they are the divinely authoritative guide for our faith, belief, and manner of living.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>